Women's Rights Collection, 1789-2000 (bulk 1864-1983)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. CONFERENCES
  - Conventions
    - American Equal Rights Association, NY: proceedings1867 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - National Women's Rights Convention of 1850: Lisa Connolly Cook: M.A. thesis2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- SERIES IV. EQUAL RIGHTS AMENDMENT
  - General and pre-1970
    - Alice Paul: clippings, telegram, correspondence, and photographs1939-76 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Clippings1957-81 (Box 21, Folder 2-7)
    - Reports, correspondence, and printed materials1898-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1-9)
    - Freedom Train documents (list)n.d. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Anti-ERA: clippings, book, articles, statements, and pamphlets1924-75 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Post- 1970
    - The Fight for ERA (oral history project)1983 (Box 22)
      [NOTE: audio cassette tapes are closed. * CD use copies of some tapes available in boxes 56-57]
      - Accession records, contents list, and memo (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Interview schedule and questions (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Adams, Ruth: interview notes, photographs, and 3 tapes (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Atkins, Carol: interview notes, photographs, and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Bonk, Kathy: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes * (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Butler, Pat and Twiss: interview notes, photographs and 3 tapes (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Catania, Susan: interview notes, photographs and 3 tapes * (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Ciarrochi, Lillian: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Cohan, Alice: interview notes and photographs (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Collins, Mary Jean: interview notes (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Crisp, Mary: interview notes and photographs (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Cutri, Diane: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Dunn, Betsy: interview notes, photographs and 3 tapes (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - East, Catherine: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes * (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Edwards, Don: interview notes, photographs and 1 tapes (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Ferguson, Vicki: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes * (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Frank, Pat: interview notes and 1 tape (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Ghizzoni, Audrey: interview notes and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Greenwald, Sheila: interview notes, photographs and 1 tape * (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Heath, Mariwyn: interview notes and 2 tapes * (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Jeffrey, Mildred: interview notes and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Leopold, Beth: interview notes and 2 tapes (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Lewis, Ann: interview notes, program, photographs, and 1 tape (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Roberts, Colette: interview notes and 2 tapes * (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Sackman, Reed Gloria: interview notes photographs, and 4 tapes * (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Smeal, Eleanor: interview notes and photographs (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Wells-Schooley, Jane: interview notes and photographs (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Wingard, Jinx: interview notes, photographs and 2 tapes (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Yard, Molly: interview notes and photographs (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Yard, Molly and Alice Cohan: interview notes and photographs (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General: articles, paper, and pamphlets1970-83 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Common Cause: memos and pamphlets1972-74 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Citizens' Advisory Council: pamphlets1970-76 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ERAmerica: mailings, correspondence, pamphlets, and articles1976-77 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - League of Women Voters: "weather report" and pamphlet, circa 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and pamphlets1970-78 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bibliographies and pamphlets1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - NOW: information packet, pamphlets, petition, flyer, and newspaper1971-78 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Pamphlets and articles1970-77 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Inc.: pamphlets and background material, circa late 1970s (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Women United: pamphlet, memos, and press release1971-72 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Housewives for ERA: pamphlets and correspondence1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Pamphlets, memos, resolutions, and mailing1970-78 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Vital Issues - Center for Information on America: pamphlet1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Memorabilia: potholder, pins, matches, postcards, bumper stickers, invitation, and information packetn.d., [See also box 25a] (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Anti-ERA: correspondence, pamphlets, memos, and clippings1977 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - ERA: hearings and congressional records1970-72 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Memorabilia: mug with ERA inscriptionn.d. (Box 25a)
    - Committee to ratify the Massachusetts State Equal Rights: clippings, pamphlets, bumper sticker, and reports1975-76 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, reports, clippings, and newsletters1973-78 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- SERIES V. LEGAL STATUS
  - Harvard Women's Law Journal (Vol. 1, No. 1)Spring 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Articles and flyers1970-81 (Box 27)
  - Clippings1970-79 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Court decisions: legal docket, and clippings1970-77 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Heath, Kathryn G., Legislation and its Implications for Eliminating Sex Bias1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: clippings, correspondence, and reports1927-78 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Packard Trial: book1869 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Property rights: legislation and article1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Report of the President's Task Force on Women's Rights and Responsibilities1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Social Security: report and statement1946-78 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - National Women's Agenda: agenda1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Legal status and treatment of women: questionnaire replies1947 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Women and the Law Conference: workshops, pamphlets, and supporting materials1976-81 (Box 27, Folder 12-13)
  - Women Law Reporter: newsletters1974-75 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Women's Rights Project (American Civil Liberties Union): correspondencen.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Articles, speech, and magazine1971-74 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlets, magazine, articles, and report1901-81 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Rights of Women: workbook of international conventions relating to women's issues and concerns1983 (Box 28)
  - National League of Women Voters: pamphlets, stories, and speeches1924-48 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights - UN Assembly: pamphlets1949 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Women and the Law: report, circa 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - States
    - General
      - Surveys and articles1924-71 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Book, pamphlets, reports, and clippings1908-78 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut: clippings, newsletters, and newspapers1972-77 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts
      - General: pamphlets, clippings, papers, newsletters, and correspondence1967-75 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - CMS: petition and legislationn.d. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Bills relating to women: pamphlets1971-72 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Commission Against Discrimination: pamphlets1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Michigan: report and newsletters1973-79 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Minnesota: legislation1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey: legislationn.d. (Box 10)
    - Tennessee: clippings1912 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Blueprints for Women Conference: newspaper1976 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - National Commission on the Observance of IWY: Homemakers Committee reports1977 (Box 29)
  - The Legal Status of Homemakers in...
    - Alabama - Oregon (Box 30, Folder 1-37)
    - Pennsylvania - Wyoming (Box 31, Folder 1-13)
- SERIES VI. ORGANIZATIONS
  - National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year
    - Agenda letters1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous: memos, pamphlets, and correspondence1976-77 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Press releases1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
    - Publications1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Report "To Form a More Perfect Union," 1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Updates1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Workshop guides, circa 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
  - National Women's rights organizations: fact sheetn.d. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Anti-defamation League of B'nai B'rith: press releasen.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Equity Network: correspondence and handouts1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights for Women: handbook, mailings, and court rulings1971-73 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - International Alliance of Women: pamphlet1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Maine Women's Political Caucus: correspondence and newsletters1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Women's Political Caucus
    - General: handouts, newsletters, bylaws, correspondence, pin, clippings, and pamphlets1971-83 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Plenary Session: information1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - November Caucus, Boston College: agenda and pamphlet1971 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Second Plenary Session: agenda1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Clippings1971-72 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - National Advisory Committee for Women: clippings1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - National Women's Education Fund: poster and correspondence1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - National Women's Political Caucus: pin, agenda, statements, workshop information, pamphlets, clippings, and articles1971-76, [see also cassette tapes on shelf] (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
  - North Carolina Women's Political Caucus: clippings1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Oregon Women's Political Caucus: newspaper1977 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvanians for Women's Rights: newsletters1973 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - The Women's Commission in Exile: newsletters1982-83 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Women's Political Caucus: clippings1971 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Women USA: correspondence and pamphlets1980 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Women's Action Alliance: pamphlets, press releases, correspondence, and agenda1976-79 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Women's Coalition for the Third Century: pamphlets, correspondence, articles, and pin1974-76 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Women's Commission in Exile - Massachusetts: pamphlets, annual report, and newsletters1979-81 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Women's Equity Action League: pamphlets, press releases, articles, and memos1971-78 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Women's Lobby, Inc.: correspondence, newsletters, and pamphlets1973-78 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous women's rights organizations: clippings1971 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- SERIES VII. COMMISSIONS ON THE STATUS OF WOMEN
  - Publications
    - Statement by the President on the Establishment of the President's Commission on the Status of Women (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Home and Community1963 (Box 34)
    - American Women1963-68 (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Private Employment1963 (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Federal Employment1963 (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Protective Labor Legislation1963 (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Social Insurance and Taxes1963 (Box 34)
    - Report of the Committee on Education1963 (Box 34)
  - Report request forms1964-65 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Clippings1963 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Press release1963 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Commission meetings: reports, agendas, press releases, correspondence, pamphlets, and minutes1961-63 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
  - Executive letters: executive letters to members of the commission with press releases, and reports1962-63 (Box 36)
  - Reports of the Committee on Educationn.d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Committee on Federal Employment Policies and Practices1963 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Reports of the Committee on Social Insurance and Taxes: pamphlets1962-63 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Committee on Political and Social Rights1963 (Box 40)
  - Reports and articles1961-63 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Agenda, reports, minutes, and memos1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Private Employment: background facts1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Press releases and proposals1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Protective Labor Legislation: pamphlets, memos, and reports1962-68 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Citizens' Advisory Council on the Status of Women
    - Women in Women in 1975 (6 reports)1970- (Box 42, Folder 1-6)
  - Committee on Home and Community: memos, agendas, reports, and pamphlets1962-72 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous publications
    - Women Today: Trends and Issues, by Dr. Caroline F. Ware1962 (Box 43)
    - American Women (3 copies)1963 (Box 43)
    - Background Memorandum of the Status of Women, by Dr. Caroline F. Ware1962 (Box 43)
    - Report on Four Consultations, by the Commission1963 (Box 43)
    - Report of the Committee on Private Employment, by the Commission1963 (Box 43)
    - Report of the Committee on Social Insurance and Taxes, by the Commission1963 (Box 43)
    - A Brief in favor of an Equal Rights Amendment (3 copies) presented by National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs1963 (Box 43)
    - Women (in 1972), by Citizens' Advisory Council, on the Status of Women (2 copies)1973 (Box 43)
    - Report on Progress in 1965 on the Status of Women, by Citizens' Advisory Council, on the Status of Women, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Report of the Committee on Protective Labor Legislation1963 (Box 43)
    - Report of the Committee on Federal Employment (2 copies)1963 (Box 43)
  - Follow-up reports
    - Interdepartmental Committee and Citizens' Advisory Council on the Status of Women: Progress Reports1964-66 (Box 44)
    - Report on Four Consultations1963
      - American Women1963-68 (Box 44)
      - Report of the Task Force on Family Law and Policy1968 (Box 44)
      - Women in 1970 - Women in 1975 (6 reports) 1970-75 (Box 44)
      - Press release concerning new appointments1969 (Box 44)
    - Report of the Task Force on Labor Standards, 1968
      - Report of the Task Force on Health and Welfare1968 (Box 44)
      - Progress and Prospects1965 (Box 44)
  - The President's Task Force on Women's Rights and Responsibilities: press releases, bill, and reports1961-70 (Box 44)
  - State Commissions on the Status of Women
    - Alabama: bulletin and statement1951-71 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - California: bulletin1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Colorado: summary report1965 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut: annual report1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Florida: annual report1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Hawaii: reports, newsletter, and book1966-77 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Iowa: article1975 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Kentucky: Kentucky Women1964 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Maryland: legislation1971 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts: clippings, reports, correspondence, and newsletters1974-75 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Michigan: report1968 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Minnesota: annual reportn.d. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey: report1964 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - New York: pamphlets1964-77 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: report1964 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Oregon: report1965 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania: remarks, report, newsletter, and pamphlet1965-73 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Texas: pamphlet1958 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Utah: report1966 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Washington: reports1963-78 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Wisconsin: reports and newsletter1965-76 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- SERIES VIII. COUNTRIES
  - General: note cards, clippings, articles, and packets1973-80 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - United Nations: clippings, articles, and pamphlets1968-75 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Africa1972-80 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Albania1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Asia1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Australia1962-73 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Canada (Box 46)
    [see box 47]
  - China1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - England (Box 46)
    [see box 48]
  - France (Box 46)
  - Germany1871-1944 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Israel/ Jerusalem - Arabs1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Italy1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Japan1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Lebanon1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Mexico1974-80 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Norway1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Pakistan1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Philippines1980 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Portugal1973-74 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - San Marino1973 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Spain1980 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Thailand1973 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Turkeyn.d. (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam1973 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Canada
    - La Bonne Parole: pamphlets and newspapers1917-58 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Canadian Advisory Council on the Status of Women: pamphlets1982 (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - Clippings1953-60 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Casgrain, Madame. Pierra F.: clipping, pamphlet, and transcriptn.d. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Le Code Civil: articles and pamphlets1943-49 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Legal status of married women: pamphlets, correspondence, and clippings1924-64 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - National Action Committee: pamphlets, circa 1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Nationality of married women: pamphlet1959 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Status Anyone?: pamphlet1972 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - England
    - General: pamphlets, clippings, and A Woman's Place1850-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Nationality rights: pamphlets1925-46 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets and books1866-1976 (Box 48, Folder 3-5)
    - Alfred B. Wallace: correspondence1913 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Wollstonecraft, Mary: pamphlets, correspondence, articles, and engraving, circa 1876 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Facsimile of a Deed by a Single Lady of land in the Manor of Naudelsleigh, Lancasshire, England(poster)1318 (Box 48)
  - France
    - General: clippings, pamphlets, and book1871-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Early History: books and articles1888-1893 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Condorcet, Marquis de: pamphlets1789 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Gallant, Mavis: "Annals of Justice," 1971 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - The Fight for ERA (oral history project): original cassette tapes and preservation CDs [CLOSED] (Box 52-55)
  - The Fight for ERA (oral history project):-in-house use copies (CDs) (Box 52-55)
    - Bonk, Kathy [digital file copy available] (Box 56)
    - Catania, Susan (Box 56)
    - East, Catherine (Box 56)
    - Ferguson, Vicki (Box 56)
    - Greenwald, Sheila [digital file copy available] (Box 56)
    - Heath, Marilyn (Box 56)
    - Roberts, Colette (Box 57)
    - Sackman-Reed Gloria (Box 57)
  - International Women's Year, National Women's Conference: 48 cassette tapes 1977 (Box on shelf)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, keynote speeches, San Jose, California (6 audiocassettes) Sept 9-11, 1997 (Box on shelf)
- ADDED MATERIALS
  - International Women's Year (IWY) conference, Puerto Rico: minutes, agendas, correspondence, resolutions, and program materials1976-78 (Box 51 (os))
- OVERSIZE MATERIAL
  - New York State Women's Meeting: report1977 (Box 49)
  - Winifred Harper Cooley: scrapbook of articles re: women's rightscirca 1920s (Box 50)
  - "Representative Women," Lithograph by L. Grozelier (Lucretia Mott, Harriet Beecher Stowe, Abby Kelley Foster, Lucy Stone, Lydia Maria Child, Antoinette Brown Blackwell, Maria Weston Chapman)1857 (Box 51)
  - The Fight for ERA(oral history project): original cassette tapes and preservation copies1983 (Box 52-55)
  - The Fight for ERA(oral history project): CD use copies1983 (Box 56-57)
  - Equal Rights Amendment: editorials and press comments1943-44 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Exhibit material (IWY conference, Houston): photographs and printed material1977 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Fac-simile of a Deed by a Single Lady... (poster), 1318 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Poster, "The Time is Now," (for benefit of women candidates)1992 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Proclamation of Women's History Month1999 (signed by Bill Clinton) (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Side-by-Side (phonograph record album): re-enactments of scenes from women's history1848-1920 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Seneca Falls Centennial (1948): newspaper, 1948 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Stone, Lucy (Blackwell): clipping from Woman's Journal1893 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
  - Miscellaneous posters (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
    - ERA (2)n.d. (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
    - Conference on Women in Beijing (2)1995 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
    - Dutch women's rightsn.d. (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
    - U.S. National Women's AgendaJun 1975 (Map-case Flat File Dwr 8)
- ITEMS ON SHELF
  - Allen, Angela Z., 50-50 Gender Balance
  - Alexander, Shana, Women's Legal Rights1975
  - Blackwell, Alice Stone, What I Owe to My Father1931, 1999
  - Davis, Paulina W., A History of the National Woman's Rights Movement1871
  - Discrimination Against Women (Parts I and II), Hearings, U.S. House Committee on Education and Labor, Special Subcommittee on Education1970
  - Equal Rights, Hearings, U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary1970
  - The "Equal Rights" Amendment, Hearings, U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary, Subcommittee on Constitutional Amendments1970
  - The Federal Civil Rights Enforement Effort, Report of the U.S. Commission on Civil RightsNov 1974
  - First New York State Women's Meeting (volumes I and II): report1977
  - Women's Rights Pamphlets, Cornell University Collection (microfiche)1814-1912
  - Fishman, Nathaniel, Married Woman's Bill of Rights, intro by Dorothy Kenyon1943
  - Holley, Marietta, Samantha Among the Brethren1890
  - IWY National Women's Conference: Official Briefing Book1977
  - Keep Your Laws Off My Body, compilation of clippings, hearings, lawsuitsn.d.
  - Report of the Women's Action Program, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare1972
  - The Spirit of Houston1978
  - Status of Women in Canada1970
  - ...To Form a More Perfect Union..., Report of the National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year1975, 1976
  - Woman's Centennial Congress1940
  - Woman's Rights Pamphlets (bound volume)n.d.
  - Women and the Law1981
  - Miscellaneous publications (photocopies)
    [NOTE: many of these are duplicates of pamphlets and articles located in SERIES I. GENERAL]
    - Woman's Rights Almanac1858
    - The Rights and Conditions of Women by Samuel J. May, 1846
    - Letters to Dupont De L'Eure on the Political Position of Women by Emma Willard1848
    - Enfranchisement of Women1851
    - Education of Females by Paulina W. Davis1851
    - Sanctity of Marriage by E. Oakes Smithn.d.
    - Responsibilities of Woman by C.I.H Nichold1851
    - Letter from Mrs. Elizabeth C. Stanton1850
    - Women's Rights1853
    - The Elective Franchise by Geo William Curtis1858